So as you see, we checked and we saw that wow, this text looks so much like it is generated by AI
And for example, we want to provide it somewhere that we don't want them to understand that what we just created is
Created by AI. So what we do over here is that we come to AI
Humanizer. So this is another tool that we have with Quilbot. I click on AI humanizer
in order
To use the tool for this very article of mine. I'm very concerned about
The problem the big problem that we have which is
It's highly detectable that will text his AI. So let's see what Quilbot can do for us
Paste or type any text whether a human or AI generated into Quilbot's AI humanizer to make it sound more authentic in natural
right, so I
Paste my text over here and we have two modes over here basically. We have basic in advance. So I
Do it with basic
Oh, okay
so
Huh, so there's a lot of words the maximum words for the free plan is
25 words, right? So let me remove all of this
And let me come back and try to do it with
No more than
125 words, right? So the first paragraph only so if I click on human eyes and I wait
Let's see what it does with the conversions
So how to start learning friends as a foreigner a complete beginner's guide so it converts this
It's convex it to a comprehensive beginner's guide to learning friends as a foreigner
One of the most fulfilling experiences you can have is learning French
So what was it previously learning French is one of the most rewarding journeys you can take yeah
Most rewarding journeys. It's so weird
JTPT no offense, but it is so weird
But as you see it is humanizing it for us. So
It's pretty cool